MD GOLAM ROBBANI

H#27, R#09, PC Culture housing society, mohammadpur, Dhaka-1207

Email: robbaniamld@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/mohammad-golam-robbani-04

Cell: 01816 040404



> CAREER OBJECTIVE

To pursue a challenging career in your dynamic organization in relevant arena, where the opportunities to learn, grow and take responsibilities. Secure a responsible career opportunity to fully utilize my training and skills.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

MSS (SOCIAL WORK)
GOVT. TITUMIR COLLEGE
NATIONAL UNIVERSITY
SECOND CLASS, PASSING YEAR 2009

BSS (SOCIAL WORK)
GOVT. TITUMIR COLLEGE
NATIONAL UNIVERSITY
SECOND CLASS, PASSING YEAR 2008

HSC (HUMANITIES)
GOVT. SHERPUR COLLEGE
CGPA 3.4 OUT OF 5, B GRADE, PASSING YEAR 2004

Diploma (Hotel management)
WESTERN INSTITUTE OF BUSINESS & TECHNOLOGY
CGPA 3.4 OUT OF 4, PASSING YEAR 2002

SSC (SCEINCE)
BAKSHIGANJ NM HIGH SCHOOL
FIRST DIVISION, PASSING YEAR 1999

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING

Certification	Trained by	Duration	Year
Customer Centricity	KAAS (India)	One Month	2018
Certificate course (MS Word & Excel)	Bangladesh National Computer Training Institute	Three Month	2007

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

Language	Reading	Writing	Speaking	
Bengali	High	High	High	
English	High	High	Medium	

> CAREER SUMMARY

I have 12+ years full time experience in enabling clients throughout radically improve career outcomes. My working experience sales & recovery arena at first joined as a sales executive at Pioneer Distributions Ltd Authorized Distributor of Grameen Phone after two years I joined Land development company Amin Mohammad Group as an officer direct sales, after two years switched to Automobiles company as an executive Rangs motors Limited after two years get promotion as a senior executive and second time promotion as an Assistant manager responsibility as a zonal head credit management once more time switched now I am serving Alif Motors Limited as a manager head of recovery.

> EXPERIENCE DETAILS

JANUARY 2020 – TO CONTINUE MANAGER, HEAD OF RECOVERY

ALIF MOTORS LIMITED

RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Team work concept to approach everyone working in a team will you fulfill your dreams.
- Focus on realizing one's dreams, achieving those goals by working in teams.
- Setting monthly target goals from current EMI with overdue & junk file.
- Monitoring monthly credit collection and lead branch manager & collection executive for credit collection.
- To keep close contact with all customers & acknowledge with them time to time.
- Ensure daily collection of monthly installment date wise & posting software.
- Maintain effective communication and good relationship with customers for various line functions.
- Ensure pre sales inspection & verification for delivery after confirmation of booking.
- Coordinate with service center for resolving any service related problem of the customer.
- Responsible for seized vehicle on failing to pay installment.
- Ensure necessary arrangements for various Inspection & verification of customers and check the forms and formats accurately.
- Prepare recovery reports on regular basis and send to higher management.
- Liaison Conscious in any recovery crisis and any critical situation.
- Ensure that business risks and controls are well managed as per internal policy and regulatory framework.
- Softly calculatedly done final settlement and ownership transfer of the respective customer.
- Ensure compliance of internal process, policies and guidelines, rules & regulation.
- Monitoring & Letter issue to the party and take necessary legal action if require.
- Prepare daily/weekly work plan, collection plan and monthly tour plan and submit to higher management.

JUNE 2013 – DECEMBER 2019

ASISTANT MANAGER, ZONAL HEAD

RANGS MOTORS LIMITED

- Prepare daily/weekly/monthly work plan and prediction submit to higher management.
- Communicate clearly and consistently to subordinate & senior management in regard to goals and current market conditions.
- Monitoring and lead branch in charge & executive for achieve target goals.
- Established positive relationship with Customer, sales executive, service center, dealers & back Office.
- Develop sales & recovery team through ride-along coaching, participating in client meetings, feedback, training and career path opportunities.
- Managing automotive customer expectations and spend time with team executive visiting customer in the field.
- To keep close contact with all customers & acknowledge with them time to time.
- Forecasting and establishing monthly and annual performance objectives.
- Create best effort for smart prediction, target & hard work with full team for achieving goals.
- Special offer disbursed and gift for various occasions with connecting with clients/customers.
- Consistently provides relevant feedback to team & clients. Assure quality prediction, time frame work & target wise achievement.
- Identify & growth opportunities key, skilled, techniques, experience, competitive environment.
- Apply for best achievement practices to create and execute successful growth.

FEBRUARY 2010 TO FEBRUARY 2013

OFFICER, DIRECT SALES

AMIN MOHAMMAD GROUP

- Established positive relationship with visit customers & back Office.
- Develop sales & recovery team through ride-along coaching, participating client meet, feedback, training and career path opportunities.
- Try to understand customer expectations and spend time visiting customer in the field.
- Communicate clearly and consistently to senior management in regard to pricing strategy, business development goals and current market conditions.
- Forecasting and establishing monthly and annual performance objectives.
- Create smart prediction, monthly target goals, special offer disbursed and gift for various occasions with connecting with clients/customers.
- Daily make report positive client visit, Positive over phone customer & before field visit customer.

APRIL 2008 TO JANUARY 2010

OFFICER, DIRECT SALES

PIONEER DISTRIBUTION LTD

- Every day physical meet with point of sales for collect order.
- Requirements wise product delivery and received cent percent cash.
- Route plan wise visit every POS try to create new POS.
- Push for huge stock for every shop. Positive relationship with customers.
- Collect last day sale customer form for confirm activate.

> EXTRA CRRICULAM ACTIVITIES:

• CREATIVITY • INTERPERSONAL SKILLS • CRITICAL THINKING • PROBLEM SOLVING • PUBLIC SPEAKING • TEAMWORK SKILLS • ACTIVE LISTENING • NEGOTIATION • SOCIAL WORK, VOLUNTEERING AND CHARITY WORK • DECISION MAKING • CUSTOMER SERVICE • LEADERSHIP SKILLS • ENGLISH LANGUAGE SKILLS AND SO ON.

> PERSONAL DETAILS:

Father's Name : Md Mozammal Haque

Mother's Name : Angura Haque
Date of Birth : May 1, 1984

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Married

Nationality : Bangladeshi

National Id No. : 3910711364508

Religion : Islam
Passport No : 0757516

Permanent Address : Vill: Tangari para, PO:murar para, PS: Bakshiganj, District: Jamalpur

> REFERENCES:

Name : Md Moshi Uddin Salam Abu bakar mozumder uzzal

Organization: Rangs Motors LimitedAlif Motors LimitedDesignation: Assistant General ManagerManaging DirectorMobile: +8801711060789+8801708483501E-Mail: salam@rangsgroup.comuzzal@alifmotors.com

Relation : Professional Professional

My experience, abilities & information in this resume is true and correct to the best of my knowledge. I take every responsibility, word that has been mentioned in the above.

Signature

Date: